Hello friends, welcome to our YouTube channel.
Friends, in today's video
we will talk about ICC Bank.
Friends, many vacancies have been announced in the Finance and Incense Department in ICC Bank
and
whatever is its vacancy in over India, your P code will be
P code 22, you will get it, but
friends, let me tell you in the beginning that this vacancies are
free of cost, there is
no charge for it, it is absolutely free and I will
also tell you the mobile number, you can call that number and if you want to get
complete information,
you will get it, so
friends, let's move ahead and
before moving ahead, if you have
not subscribed to our channel, then subscribe and do it as well,
so that
whatever banking information comes in future, first of all
you should
show its details on our website, along with
this I will tell you
what educational qualification is required in it and
which skills you must have for the banking sector here, I will
give you information about it, so first of all let's
talk, friends,
how much limit do you need here, then the limit will be given to
you  You should be between 18 and 35 years of age.
Apart from this, friends, if you are 12th pass
with experience, graduation or post
graduation, then you can also apply for this.
Along with this, friends, I want to
tell you that there is something necessary in this, you should have good
communication skills. Along with this,
you should also have computer knowledge. If you do not need high-fi
computer knowledge, if you have basic computer
knowledge then you can be eligible. Let's
talk to friends about how to apply.
Friends, you can find this on our website.
After going there, I will give you a complete answer.
After that, you will be
given a phone number to apply. You can apply by phone.
Friends, I will provide their email ID.
If you want to apply through the official website, then
you can also apply through ICC. If
you
want to apply in any other bank, whether you are in ICC
Bank, Axis Bank, HDFC Bank,
then this is a great opportunity for you. I have
already made a video for you.
You can check out the place here. There are
many here.  While the
information is given in the big and
even after giving it, if you do not feel like it then our
friends will give you a form given below,
file out that form, it will be sent to
you from our side tomorrow and here
friends, you can also get the release of their PET course
directly in the bank,
okay so go friends, in today's video, the
link of all has been provided in the description below, that's all
in this video, if you
like the video then like, share and subscribe,
thank you